<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Project name="DT Roles and Groups">
	<Package name="GUI">
		<Key ID="STR_AW_Role_Menu_Title">
			<English>Role Selection</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_AW_Role_Menu_Default_Loadout">
			<English>DEFAULT LOADOUT</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_AW_Repair_Description">
			<English>The Repair Specialist responsible for keeping vehicles operational through repairing and maintaining them.</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_AW_Medic_Description">
			<English>The Medic is responsible for keeping his squad in the fight through treating and reviving his squad mates.</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_AW_Engineer_Description">
			<English>The Engineer has the combined features of both Repair Specialists and Explosive Specialists.</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_AW_TL_Description">
			<English>The Team Leader takes command of a small team in the field. Gets access to Light Anti Tank weaponry and Grenade Launchers</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_AW_SL_Description">
			<English>The Squad Leader takes command of an infantry squad, utilising all members to achieve the objectives. Gets access to Light Anti Tank weaponry and Grenade Launchers</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_AW_EOD_Description">
			<English>The Explosive Specialist can track and defuse explosives, as well as setup explosives to aid his team.</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_AW_Sniper_Description">
			<English>The Sniper has access to long range weaponry and ghillie suits to assist friendlies from afar.</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_AW_Spotter_Description">
			<English>The Spotter aids the Sniper by choosing targets and acting as close protection.</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_AW_Pilot_Description">
			<English>The Pilot is responsible for transporting troops, vehicles and supplies around the AO. They can also fly CAS Missions to assist friendlies on the ground.</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_AW_UAV_Description">
			<English>The UAV Operator can command UAV's and UGV's to assist friendly forces.</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_AW_Marksman_Description">
			<English>The Marksman provides accurate medium- to long-range fire support, bridging the gap between rifleman and sniper.</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_AW_HAT_Description">
			<English>The Heavy Anti-Tank (HAT) Specialist is equipped to destroy armored threats using high-powered launchers and guided munitions.</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_AW_LAT_Description">
			<English>The Light Anti-Tank (LAT) Specialist engages light armor and fortified positions using portable launchers and disposable rockets.</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_AW_AR_Description">
			<English>The Automatic Rifleman lays down suppressive fire with a light machine gun, enabling teammates to maneuver under cover.</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_AW_Grenadier_Description">
			<English>The Grenadier provides indirect fire support using a grenade launcher to suppress enemies, clear buildings, and deny cover.</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_AW_JTAC_Description">
			<English>The JTAC (Joint Terminal Attack Controller) coordinates airstrikes and artillery, acting as the crucial link between ground forces and supporting firepower.</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_AW_Mortar_Description">
			<English>The Mortarman operates indirect fire systems to provide sustained bombardment and area denial at long ranges.</English>
		</Key>
	</Package>
</Project>
